(Raj:)And I'm from India, so I know how to do it.
(Raj:)Okay.
Yeah, thank you. This means a lot to me.
(Raj:)My friends are like my family.
(Raj:)Unless you don't like them,
in which case, they're dead to me.
- You ever spent a long time in a boat before?
- Yeah.
(Bernadette:)Are you referring to the time we got stuck
on the Small World ride at Disneyland?
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
(Howard:)I'm proud of you, Leonard.
Working out on the North Sea for months?
That's really something.
(Leonard:)I know.
(Leonard:)As far as science goes,
this is the adventure of a lifetime.
Ha, ha. Maybe your lifetime, I went to space.
(Leonard:)It's not a competition.
(Howard:)You're right, you're right.
(Howard:)I'm really proud of you,
and I'm gonna miss you when you're gone.
(Howard:)And space beats water.
(Amy:)Rajesh, I thought Lucy was coming.